Daniyar Gabdullin

Back-end developer

Email: dannygabdullin@gmail.com Address: Almaty, 1-mcr, 12 Phone: +7 (708) 755-6862 Date of birth: 06-18-1995 Nationality: Kazakh

ABOUT ME

I am a Tech Enthusiast with 1 years of Web Development experience with Django.

I consider myself more of a backender than frontender. Some tech that I am interested to learn in near future are: React.js, Node.js and maybe something related to Data Science.

EXPERIENCE

October 2020 - Present

Freelance

Developing and maintaining the website, front and back-end functionality of the website to produce clean code that follows the design and functional specifications.

Developed custom front-end HTML, CSS, Javascript.

Use PostreSQL, MySQL

Github - github.com/GabdoDoni

Almaty
October 2019 - Present

Engineer

Универсал-Реклама

Developed an engineering library for the Company to store drawings, calculations and backup material from previous projects and proposal efforts.

Coordinated drawings with designers and clients.

Calculated and ordered the required amount of materials.

Atyrau, Tengiz September 2017 - September 2019

Supply Engineer

Nasar Solutions

Manage the practical application of supply chain technology and interfaces.

Engage the supply chain organization in addressing continuous improvement and change/project management gaps in order to develop strategic action plans for improvement.

Conduct analysis and develop recommendations on various supply chain strategy projects that involve complex cost/benefit tradeoffs, e.g..

EDUCATION

Almaty

October 2020 - February 2021

Uralsk

September 2013 - June 2017

Uralsk

September 2014 - January 2017

Back-end developer

KnewIT

Mechanical Engineer

West Kazakhstan Agrarian-Technical University

Military Naval Department

West Kazakhstan Agrarian-Technical University

SKILLS LANGUAGES

- Python
- Django
- HTML/CSS
- MySQL
- PostreSQL
- JavaScript (Basic)
- OOPGit

- Kazakh
- Fluent

Russian Fluent

English

Pre-intermediate